wpcanada.ca 2013-06-09

# Privacy Policy » WPCanada

**Introduction**  
WPCanada is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our privacy practices and how that may pertain to you.

**Third Party Host**  
This website is hosted on a third party service provider known as HostGator. Any information you choose to send to us is stored on the servers of HostGator.com LLC.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small text files placed on your computer by the many websites you visit. We use cookies in order to make your visit more convenient by offering more functionality such as remembered form fill ins. This website also participates in the Google Analytics program which utilizes cookies to collect anonymous traffic data. Please see the section entitled Log Files to see how that information is used.

Cookies only track the current browser session and do not reveal, record or transmit any personal information about you to us. At no time is data ever stored on your computer. Cookies are easily deleted regardless of the browser you are using. You can read more about the use of cookies at www.cookiecentral.com

**Log Files**  
We keep a record of the domains that visit us and log the IP addresses for archival purposes only. This is accomplished via our server logs as well as data collected through Google Analytics. This information cannot be used to identify you. We will never publish the IP addresses of those who have visited us nor will we ever share that information with anyone unless:

  * we are required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request

**Polls**  
This is an interactive feature whereby users may reply to a question via a vote system. The IP addresses of those who vote are automatically logged. The poll also utilizes cookies. This is to try to prevent multiple votes from the same party. Your IP address will not be published or shared.

**Email**  
When submitting a communique to us via the [Contact Form](http://wpcanada.ca/contact/ "Contact"), you are required to provide a valid email address. This is for 2 reasons,

  * To prove that you are not an automated script
  * If you require a response

You may also voluntarily provide your email address when subscribing to our Email Updates feature.

Your email address will remain private. We will never sell, trade or otherwise share it with anyone without your consent. However, the content of any message sent to us shall be considered public unless otherwise requested by you.

It should be noted that our email subscription feature is handled by Feedburner, a Google property. We have no control over how they may use information you provide them with via this website. You are encouraged to read their [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ "Google Privacy Policy").

If you do not wish to voluntarily provide your email address to access our email subscription feature you can still subscribe to this website’s content through our [RSS feed](http://wpcanada.ca/feed/ "Full content feed").

**Links**  
This website contains many links to other websites over which we have no control. You are encouraged to familiarize yourself with their Privacy Policies as they may differ from ours.

**Policy Changes**  
We may periodically update this Privacy Policy. If so, the updated version will appear here. You are encouraged to review this document from time to time for any changes.

**Further**  
If you do not agree with these terms then you should not use this website.

_Last updated: 27 Aug 2012_
